<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MarkTranslator</string>
    <string name="button_translate">Translate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_translate">TranslateActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_select">SelectActivity</string>
    <string name="title_select">Back</string>
    <string name="title_translate">Back</string>

    <!-- indicator -->
    <string name="footer_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="footer_go">Go!</string>
    <string name="footer_back">Back</string>
    <string name="footer_next">Next</string>

    <!-- translate -->
    <string name="title_alumi">Aluminum Can Identification Mark for Beverages</string>
    <string name="text_alumi">This mark is an identification mark for promoting sorting collection and recycling of aluminum beverage cans. Labeling on aluminum cans is mandatory according to the Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources. Beer and carbonated drinks, juice, tea, coffee, canned drinking water etc.</string>
    <string name="title_asc">ASC Mark</string>
    <string name="text_asc">This mark certifies sustainable marine products acquired by protecting the nature and resources of the sea, and is doing an effort to attach an ecolabel. Similarly, there is a mechanism to certify marine products by aquaculture as well as natural marine products. Aquaculture edition This is the certification system of the ecolabel ASC of the sea. We do not place a big burden on the environment, certify aquaculture business that takes into consideration the local community, paste the ecolabel to the market and consumers so that you can see at a glance that it is a responsible aquaculture fishery product.</string>
    <string name="title_atsui">High Temperature Attention</string>
    <string name="text_atsui">There is a part to become high temperature, it may cause burns if you touch it.</string>
    <string name="title_battery">Battery Recycle Mark</string>
    <string name="text_battery" formatted="false">This mark is a mark for easily identifying that it is a product using waste paper as a raw material. The requirement of products that can display it is to use waste paper as a raw material in principle, more than 40% in principle, but toilet paper and paper are paper which used 100% raw material as a rule, copy paper And newsprint paper used more than 50% of waste paper in principle as a raw material. Since products other than paper such as cellulose fibers used for insulation materials and other materials in addition to paper and paper products as well as pet litter are also available for products using waste paper, these are also subject to marking I will. In addition, cardboard boxes and paper boxes used for packaging various goods are subject to marking, considering the box itself as a product, if waste paper is used for the paper material of the box.</string>
    <string name="title_bunkai">Do Not Disassemble the Product</string>
    <string name="text_bunkai">Do not disassemble the product. Cause of an electric shock or injury.</string>
    <string name="title_cfp">Carbon Footprint Mark</string>
    <string name="text_cfp">CFP is an abbreviation for Carbon Footprint of Products. It is a mechanism to display the products and services in an easy-to-understand manner by converting the amount of greenhouse gas emissions released throughout the entire life cycle from raw materials procurement of products and services to disposal and recycling into CO2.We will calculate the environmental impact quantitatively using the LCA method. By sharing \"awareness\" of CO2 emissions reduction action between business operators and consumers and using information visualized, businesses will cooperate with companies that form the supply chain to further reduce CO 2 emissions Promote volume reduction. We aim to make ourselves change ourselves to a lower-carbon consumer life by using \"information visualized\" information.</string>
    <string name="title_co2cf">Carbon Offset Certification Label</string>
    <string name="text_co2cf">This label is granted to projects certified by the carbon offset system to individual carbon offsetting efforts under the Ministry of the Environment\'s Carbon Offset Third Party Certification Criteria. We aim to disseminate reliable carbon · offset efforts, to recognize greenhouse gas emissions by citizens and business operators, and to promote further reduction efforts.</string>
    <string name="title_co2cn">Carbon-Neutral Label</string>
    <string name="text_co2cn">This label is granted to projects certified individually by the carbon offset system based on the Carbon Offset Third Party Certification Criteria of the Ministry of the Environment. It aims to disseminate highly reliable carbon-neutral efforts, to recognize greenhouse gas emissions by business operators, and to promote further reduction efforts.</string>
    <string name="title_cp">CP Mark</string>
    <string name="text_cp">Building parts evaluated as having certain crime prevention performance are published and published in \"Building parts inventory with high crime prevention performance\" and are called \"crime prevention building parts\", and the use of \"CP mark\" is permitted.The crime prevention building parts are 3,288 items of 17 kinds as of the end of February, \"Common designation\" and \"common mark\" have been established in order to promote the dissemination of \"building parts with high crime prevention performance\" at the joint government-private conference on development and dissemination of building parts with high crime prevention performance. CP is an initial letter of Crime Prevention, it is a mark that can be displayed only by \"security building parts\" that cleared the performance test by the \"public-private joint meeting\".</string>
    <string name="title_danboru">Recycling Mark of Cardboard</string>
    <string name="text_danboru">This mark is the universal recycling symbol. Recycle mark indicates that \"the cardboard can be recycled.\"</string>
    <string name="title_dentou">Traditional Mark</string>
    <string name="text_dentou">This mark is a symbol of traditional craftwork that was established to appeal to consumers with a unified image of traditional craft display and other propaganda. We will use it throughout the traditional craft industry that was designated by the Minister of Economy, Trade and Industry.</string>
    <string name="title_e">E Mark</string>
    <string name="text_e">This mark is a common mark attached by prefectures to special products made by making good use of the goodness of the region\'s raw materials.</string>
    <string name="title_eco">Eco Mark</string>
    <string name="text_eco">This mark is the environmental label that is attached to the product that has been recognized to be less impact on the environment throughout the entire life cycle over the \"waste\" from the \"production\" and to help the environment in a variety of goods (products and services).To take advantage of this mark, it is intended that your consumers make a product selection that was conscious of the environment and the companies involved will aim the formation of a sustainable society by to promote the environmental improvement efforts.</string>
    <string name="title_eco2">Eco Rail Mark</string>
    <string name="text_eco2">This mark is a mark informing the products that are being carried using the environmentally friendly cargo railway and companies actively engaged in the distribution process of products that are difficult for ordinary consumers to see.</string>
    <string name="title_energystar">International Energy Star Logo</string>
    <string name="text_energystar">International Energy Star Program \"is an international energy conservation system of office equipment implemented in nine countries and regions around the world. Standards are set so that the top 25% of products with excellent energy saving performance are suitable for product operation, sleeve, power consumption when off, etc. Products that meet this standard are allowed to use this mark .</string>
    <string name="title_f">F Mark</string>
    <string name="text_f">This mark is attached to the rice plant that Japan Rice Millers Association has certified the good manufacturing. F mark is the mark of safety and security.</string>
    <string name="title_fare">International Fair Trade Certification Label</string>
    <string name="text_fare">Fair trade is to mean fair trade, to purchase producers in developing countries at a price that guarantees fair wages and working conditions. This will support self-reliance and environmental conservation in developing countries. The international fair trade certification label is a product of international fair trade established by Fairtrade International in the entire process from production of the raw material through export / import, processing, manufacturing process to becoming a finished product as \"international fair trade certified product\" and a label to prove that the standards are being observed.</string>
    <string name="title_fsc">FSC Mark</string>
    <string name="text_fsc">The Forest Stewardship Council (FSC) is an international organization that certifies the world\'s forests that produce wood and the process of distribution and processing of wood cut from the forest. The certification is given to timber produced in a manner that can be continued economically, taking into consideration forest environmental conservation, benefiting the local community. Consumers can indirectly support the world\'s forest conservation by buying this FSC marked product. WWF is working to disseminate and promote the use of sustainable forests worldwide.</string>
    <string name="title_g">G Mark</string>
    <string name="text_g">As an indicator of \"good design\", this mark continues to play its role over more than half a century since its founding.</string>
    <string name="title_ge">Green Energy Mark</string>
    <string name="text_ge">This mark was established by the Green Energy Certification Center in May 2008 and indicates that the electric power used for manufacturing the product was covered with green electricity. A company that manufactures products is responsible for paying royalties for marks and supports generation of natural energy such as geothermal, wind power, and sunlight. The generated electricity is sold to the local electric power company, and the enterprise manufacturing the product is granted the right to list \"green energy mark\" in the target product.</string>
    <string name="title_green">Green Mark</string>
    <string name="text_green">This mark is a mark indicating that we use waste paper more than the prescribed proportion as raw material. It is displayed on products approved by the Paper Recycling Promotion Promotion Center.</string>
    <string name="title_gyunyu">Milk Carton Recycle Mark</string>
    <string name="text_gyunyu">This mark is the mark to be attached to products that use the used milk carton as a raw material.\"Milk Carton Recycle Mark Promotion Council\" is working to manage, operate and spread as well as a civic group \"Liaison Committee to consider the re-use of the national milk carton\".</string>
    <string name="title_gyunyu2">Milk Carton Reuse Mark</string>
    <string name="text_gyunyu2">This mark is a mark that can be attached to the product using used milk carton as raw material. \"Cow milk package reuse mark popularization promotion council\" is managed, administered and promoted together with citizen group \"Liaison meeting thinking about reuse of national milk carton\".</string>
    <string name="title_haccp">HACCP Mark</string>
    <string name="text_haccp">This mark is attached to the food that has been manufactured in the factory or the like in which the health management is being carried out by that has been approved by the Minister of Health, Labour and Welfare \"comprehensive sanitation management process (HACCP system).\" Currently, the \"meat product\", \"milk and dairy products, ice cream,\" \"containers and packaging pressure and heat sterilization food (retort food)\", \"fish paste products\", \"soft drink\" is defined as HACCP approval item, approval It has become a target.</string>
    <string name="title_haccpusa">US Export Fisheries Food HACCP Certified Facility Council Mark</string>
    <string name="text_haccpusa">This mark is displayed on the aquatic food of the \"to the United States, exports to the EU seafood HACCP certification facilities council\" member that the certified facility on the basis of the \"exports to the US marine food handling the manner\" that had set by the Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare.</string>
    <string name="title_hakka">Ignition Attention</string>
    <string name="text_hakka">Failure to use may cause ignition.</string>
    <string name="title_hamu">Ham and Sausage Fair Mark</string>
    <string name="text_hamu">This mark is displayed on the products of the \"ham and sausage products Fair Trade Council\" member that be deemed to have a proper display in accordance with the \"fair competition rules related to the display of ham and sausage.\"</string>
    <string name="title_haretsu">Burst Notice</string>
    <string name="text_haretsu">Failure to use may cause explosion.</string>
    <string name="title_ippan">General Notice, Warning, Danger</string>
    <string name="text_ippan">This mark is used to call attention to ignition, rupture, high temperature etc. in handling products.</string>
    <string name="title_jas">Japanese Agricultural Standard Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jas">This mark is given to products that have passed the  the inspection by the Japanese Agricultural Standards enacted by Minister of Agriculture、Forestry and Fisheries.</string>
    <string name="title_jdma">JDMA Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jdma">It is a mark that can be used by businesses who have become full members through the application review of the Japan Mail Order Sales Association, indicating that it is a regular member of the Japan Mail Order Sales Association. When becoming a regular member, a business operator can use Judomaku which indicates that it is a member of the association as a mail order advertisement, and can appeal the trust of the company to the public. Businesses who are regular members are striving to develop conscient mail-order systems by strictly observing mail ordering from the customer\'s point of view, such as introduction of high-quality products, thorough after-care, accuracy of advertisement expression. Consumers can see it as a guide for peace of mind when using mail order sales.</string>
    <string name="title_jema">JEMA Safety Standard Conformity Recognition Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jema">JEMA is an abbreviation for Japan Educational Materials Association approved by the Ministry of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology. Products marked with this mark are all \"JEMA School Teaching Materials / Teaching Safety Standards Compliant Products [Harmful Substances from Products (6 substances subject to standards for school environmental sanitation: formaldehyde, toluene, xylene, paradichlorobenzene, ethylbenzene, styrene ) Is below the standard of this association].</string>
    <string name="title_jis">Japanese Industrial Standard Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jis">This mark is given to industrial products that have passed the Japanese Industrial Standards.</string>
    <string name="title_jis2">Japanese Industrial Standard Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jis2">This mark is given to industrial products that have passed the Japanese Industrial Standards.</string>
    <string name="title_kaiten">Rotating Object Attention</string>
    <string name="text_kaiten">There are rotating parts such as motors and fans, which can cause injury if you open the lid or cover.</string>
    <string name="title_kaki">Fire Ban</string>
    <string name="text_kaki">Do not close the fire. It will cause the product to catch fire.</string>
    <string name="title_kami">Paper Pack Identification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_kami">This mark is a mark attached to a paper pack without aluminum. Under the Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources, identification indications are not mandated and voluntarily displayed by business organizations. Starting from July 2006, rules to use the basic of display as \"identification mark + slogan\". We recommend that you use \"identification mark\" + \"slogan\" as + \"development drawing\" and enlighten further promotion of recycling.</string>
    <string name="title_kanbatsuzai">Thinnings Mark</string>
    <string name="text_kanbatsuzai">It is the mark that can be displayed on the product using the thinnings.It is the mark to promote the importance of the use of such propulsion and thinnings of thinning and to contribute to the product selection of the consumer.There are two types of use of the thinned wood products and use in public awareness to the use of the mark.It is a system that the National Forestry Cooperative Federation operates to promote the enhancement of forest productivity and conservative culture of the forest resources of Japan.</string>
    <string name="title_kanden">Electrical Hazard</string>
    <string name="text_kanden">Disassembling or applying water may cause electric shock.</string>
    <string name="title_kome">Providing Rice Information Mark</string>
    <string name="text_kome">This mark is displayed on the rice that provided the result as confirmation information analyzed for taste, brand display and safety  by \"the Japan Grain Inspection Association.\"</string>
    <string name="title_kotton">Cotton Mark</string>
    <string name="text_kotton">This mark is the mark given to 100% of the product cotton. It is conditions that excellent quality and fashion of the height.</string>
    <string name="title_matanity">Maternity Mark</string>
    <string name="text_matanity">In the early pregnancy period, it is a very important time to maintain the health of your mother as well as the growth of your baby. However, as it is impossible to distinguish from the appearance, there are various difficulties for pregnant women such as \"you can not sit on the train by the train\", \"smoke of the cigarette is bothered\". We announced \"Maternity Mark\" aiming at securing safety and comfort concerning pregnancy and childbirth at the Promotion Review Committee of the National Movement Plan \"Healthy Parents and Child 21\". This mark is a woman who gets worn by pregnant women when using transportation facilities and makes it easy to show that they are pregnant women. Transportation, workplaces, eating and drinking establishments, etc. will be posted as a poster etc. with a callout, promoting the environment friendly to pregnant women.</string>
    <string name="title_mentai">Mentaiko Food Fair Mark</string>
    <string name="text_mentai">This mark is displayed on the products of the \"National Mentaiko food Fair Trade Council\" member be accepted as appropriate indication that follows \"fair competition rules related to the display of Mentaiko food.\"</string>
    <string name="title_mochi">Made in Japan Paddy Rice Glutinous Rice 100% Mark</string>
    <string name="text_mochi">This mark is displayed in the guaranteed products to be packaged rice cake that has been produced only in rice glutinous rice domestically by \"the national rice cake industrial cooperative.\"</string>
    <string name="title_moudouken">Guide Dog Mark</string>
    <string name="text_moudouken">Among the toys that were carefully designed to allow eyes and deaf children and adults to play with other people, the toy that was considered for the blind people was referred to as \" Toy \", in the package,\" Guide dog mark \"which designs\" Labrador Retriever \"which is active as\" Guide dog \"is displayed.</string>
    <string name="title_nori">Food Glue Fair Mark</string>
    <string name="text_nori">This mark is displayed on the products of the \"food glue Fair Trade Council\" member that be accepted as appropriate indication that follows \"fair competition rules related to the display of food glue.\" </string>
    <string name="title_nurete">Wet Person Prohibited</string>
    <string name="text_nurete">Do not touch the product with wet hands. Otherwise, you may get an electric shock.</string>
    <string name="title_omiyage">Fair Certification Mark of Souvenir Goods</string>
    <string name="text_omiyage">This mark will be displayed on tourist souvenirs certified by the \"National Tourism Souvenirs Fair Trade Council\" based on the \"Fair Competition Agreement on the Display of Tourism Souvenirs\".</string>
    <string name="title_online">Online Mark</string>
    <string name="text_online">This mark is a mark for making a judgment as to whether or not a consumer is an appropriate distributor when consumers use Internet mail order.As consumer complaints are on an increasing trend accompanying the recent rapid increase in Internet mail order, it is introduced to create an environment where consumers can use with confidence.A mark to be displayed on the website of a business operator jointly operated by the Japan Mail Order Sales Association and the Japan Chamber of Commerce and Industry and certified to conduct an appropriate transaction on the Internet.</string>
    <string name="title_paper">Paper containers Packaging Identification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_paper">This mark is the identification marks that be required to appear in the paper containers and packaging that is discharged from the home based on the \"Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources\".However except for the cardboard containers and packaging of aluminum not used in beverages paper pack.To facilitate the separation of when the consumer garbage the spent containers and packaging and to promote the separate collection of the municipality, the paper containers packaging are marked with identification mark.And waste separation paper by identification mark.*However, since the waste separation method is different by the municipality, please follow your house of municipality of rules when out of the home.</string>
    <string name="title_pefc">Programme for the Endorsement of Forest Certification Schemes</string>
    <string name="text_pefc">This mark includes that a forest management certification that a third party certifies that forestry is being conducted according to international standards established for sustainable forest management and a CoC certification that a third party certifies that wood produced from forest management certified forests and recycled materials are used as raw materials for a certain percentage or more.</string>
    <string name="title_sample">Plastic Containers and Packaging Identification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_sample">Based on the Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources, it is required to display in plastic containers and packaging in April 2001. (For drinking, PET bottles for soy sauce are excluded)</string>
    <string name="title_pra1">PET Bottle Identification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_pra1">This mark is a display for separating and collecting to refer to collecting it separately from similar items with the aim of using it as a recyclable resource. It was obliged to display on the PET bottle of designated display items (soft drinks, soy sauce, alcoholic beverages) from June 1993 by designation of government ordinance based on the Effective Utilization Promotion Act. In addition, milk has been added to designated items from October 30, 2007 due to amendment of milk etc. ministerial ordinance. In addition, as a result of reviewing designated labeling products accompanying the Amendment to the Volk Act, soy sauce has expanded to specific seasonings from April 1, 2008, soy sauce processed goods, mirin seasoning, vinegar, seasoning vinegar and non oil dressing have been added to the item.</string>
    <string name="title_pra2">Material Marking Mark</string>
    <string name="text_pra2">This mark is a material indication mark indicating plastic material. When plastics containers and packaging materials are written in the legal \"pla\" mark, it is recommended to use material indication by resin abbreviations (PP, PS, etc.) according to JIS K 6899 .</string>
    <string name="title_pra4">Material Marking Mark</string>
    <string name="text_pra4">This mark is a material indication mark indicating plastic material. When plastics containers and packaging materials are written in the legal \"pla\" mark, it is recommended to use material indication by resin abbreviations (PP, PS, etc.) according to JIS K 6899 .</string>
    <string name="title_psc">PSC Mark</string>
    <string name="text_psc">In consumer products, about products that to be in danger of especially harm to consumers life and body, it can not be sold, if there is no PSC mark indicating that meet the criteria on which the countries of established technology on it.And if dangerous products have been available on the open market that Japan has the right to order the measures of recovery such as in the production business person.These regulations items subject has a the specific products that self-confirmation is required are obliged and a special specific products inspection of further third-party organization in that.</string>
    <string name="title_pse">PSE Mark</string>
    <string name="text_pse">Business which manufactures or imports electrical goods must fulfill the obligations of the procedure stipulated in the law and display the PSE mark to the electrical supplies.</string>
    <string name="title_q">Q Mark</string>
    <string name="text_q">It is a mark that is permitted for items that have been inspected and passed based on the textile product comprehensive inspection standard so that consumers can purchase goods with peace of mind. Q is an acronym for quality, a certificate is issued under the name of the Q mark management committee. Items of inspection are: 1. presence / absence of fabric defects, 2. inspection of dimensions, 3. check of processing agent, 4. degree of dyeing and contraction, and 5. suitability for display.</string>
    <string name="title_r">Recycled Paper Use Mark</string>
    <string name="text_r">It is a voluntary mark indicating the ratio of waste paper pulp blending. Recycled paper pulp content ratio 100% recycled paper is used. It is set by the National Congress for Promotion of Waste Reduction (Current 3R Activity Promotion Forum).</string>
    <string name="title_rainforest">Rainforest Alliance Certification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_rainforest">This mark is displayed in the goods made in the material-made and the products in the Rainforest Alliance Certified farms and certified forests. These farms and forests are managed in accordance with the strict standards of environmental, social and economic for the purpose of accordance with the protection of wildlife, conservation of soil and water sources, workers and protection of their families and communities, improvement of the living.In recent years, coffee, chocolate, tea, fruits, cut flowers, paper, furniture, etc., where they will be displayed this certification mark to more and more goods.</string>
    <string name="title_reitou">Frozen Food Certification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_reitou">This mark is displayed in the frozen food of the members who were found to be compatible with the guidance criteria for quality and hygiene, which established the \"Japan Frozen Food Association\".</string>
    <string name="title_reitoumen">RMK Certification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_reitoumen">This mark is displayed on the frozen men of members manufactured at the factory that has cleared the quality standards and sanitary control standards set by the \"Japan Frozen Noodle Association\".</string>
    <string name="title_seisanjas">Production Information Released JAS Mark</string>
    <string name="text_seisanjas">This mark is attached to agricultural products on which information such as beef and pork in which information such as feeding and veterinary medicine administration has been published and agricultural chemicals and fertilizers used by producers are publicly disclosed.</string>
    <string name="title_sek">SEK Mark</string>
    <string name="text_sek">This mark is the certification mark of functional processed textile products. Based on ensuring safety, the General Association of Textile Evaluation Technologies Council is certifying while endeavoring to ensure certain performance.</string>
    <string name="title_sesshokui">No Contact</string>
    <string name="text_sesshokui">Do not touch it. It may cause injury or burns.</string>
    <string name="title_sf">SF Mark</string>
    <string name="text_sf">This mark is an abbreviation for Safety fireworks. It is a mark to be attached to the toy fireworks of domestic / imported goods circulating domestically which passed the inspection carried out by the Japan Fire fighting Association of the public interest corporation.</string>
    <string name="title_s">SG Mark</string>
    <string name="text_s">This mark is an abbreviation for Safety Goods. From the viewpoint of structure, material, usage, etc., we have established certification criteria that decided what is necessary as a safe product for products that may harm life or the body, and it is recognized as conforming to this standard It is only attached to the product. In case of a personal injury due to a product with SG mark In accordance with the cause of the accident and the degree of damage, there is compensation in the range of 100 million yen for each victim. It is attached to infant products / furniture / home / kitchenware, sports and leisure goods, welfare utensil products, kitchen appliances, household fitness supplies, garden products, bicycle supplies and so on.</string>
    <string name="title_shitake">Japanese Breeding Wood Dry Mushrooms Mark</string>
    <string name="text_shitake">This mark is displayed on Japanese shiitake mushroom shiitake mushrooms made by a member of the \"Japanese shrimp and dry wood shiitake mushroom shiitake promotion association\".</string>
    <string name="title_shouene">Energy Saving Mark</string>
    <string name="text_shouene">This mark indicates the extent to which energy saving standards established by the Energy Conservation Law are achieved. Products that achieve energy saving standards can display green marks, products that do not achieve can display orange marks. JIS standards have been enacted on display methods and others.</string>
    <string name="title_shougai">International Symbol Mark for People with Disabilities</string>
    <string name="text_shougai">This mark is a symbol common to the world to clearly indicate that it is a building or facility that people with disabilities can use. Regarding the use of Mark, it is stipulated by the \"Usage Guidelines\" of the International Rehabilitation Association. If you see this mark in a parking lot etc, please give us understanding and cooperation on consideration for the use of people with disabilities.</string>
    <string name="title_silver">Silver Mark</string>
    <string name="text_silver">With the arrival of a full-fledged aging society, business operators that offer high-quality services and products that enable elderly people to live in a safe manner are being sought. Silver Mark responds to the needs of such society, establishes criteria for each type of silver service, and is issued to businesses that have met firmly the criteria. It is a reliable guide for users to select businesses.</string>
    <string name="title_sq">SQ Mark</string>
    <string name="text_sq">This mark is displayed on products that have passed the \"Confectionary General Technology Center\" by examining and inspecting the items necessary for the safety and quality assurance of confectionery, further examining the contents of display and others.</string>
    <string name="title_st">ST Mark</string>
    <string name="text_st">This mark is an abbreviation for Safety toy. It is attached to products that passed ST standard conformity inspection of toy safety standards, mechanical safety, flammability safety, chemical safety. In the event of an accident in the event of an ST marked toy, we have established a compensation mutual aid system.</string>
    <string name="title_steel">Drink Volume Steel Can Identification Mark</string>
    <string name="text_steel">This mark is an identification mark for promoting separate collection and recycling of steel drink cans. Labeling on steel cans is mandatory according to the Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources. There are carbonated drinks, juice, tea, coffee, canned drinking water, some canned beer (steel can) etc.</string>
    <string name="title_steel2">General Can Material Marking Mark</string>
    <string name="text_steel2">This mark attached to a general can. In the Law for Promotion of Effective Utilization of Resources, identification indications are not obligated and voluntarily displayed by business organizations.</string>
    <string name="title_tokubetsu">Special Purpose Food Mark</string>
    <string name="text_tokubetsu">This mark is attached to foods that are permitted by the country for indications on special uses, such as infant growth, sufferers, pregnant women, nursing mothers, nursing mothers, people with difficulty in swallowing, etc. for insurance retention and recovery.</string>
    <string name="title_tokuho">Food Mark for Specified Health Use</string>
    <string name="text_tokuho">This mark is a food that can be expected to aim for a particular health, it contains the functional health component (involvement component) that affect such as the body\'s physiological function. </string>
    <string name="title_tokuteijas">Specific JAS Mark</string>
    <string name="text_tokuteijas">This mark is attached to food that meets the JAS standard for foods that meet the JAS standards for special production and manufacturing methods, or that has a feature in quality etc. compared with similar standard products.</string>
    <string name="title_umi">Sea Ecolabel</string>
    <string name="text_umi">This certification system consists of \"fishery certification\" which certifies that it is a sustainable and appropriately managed fishery and two types of CoC certification for preventing the mixture of certified marine products and non-certified marine products in the distribution / processing process It consists of certification.This certification system is operated and managed by MSC, an international NPO, and meets internationally agreed standards for certification of fishery products including eco-labeling system of FAO \"fisheries ecolabel\" and ecolabel system.</string>
    <string name="title_uni">Fair Mark of Food</string>
    <string name="text_uni">This mark will be displayed on the product of the member of the \"Food Fair Trade Council across the country\" that is deemed to be properly labeled in accordance with the \"Fair Competition Regulations on Food Display\".</string>
    <string name="title_usagi">Rabbit Mark</string>
    <string name="text_usagi">Among the toys that were designed to allow eyes and deaf children and adults to play with other people, packages of toys that were \"considered\" for people with disabilities \"Rabbit Mark\" which designs \"Rabbit\" is attached.</string>
    <string name="title_wool">Wool Mark</string>
    <string name="text_wool">This mark is \"Symbol to prove quality\" set by The Woolmark Company. Although we see a lot of wool\'s items, this mark can only be attached to products that passed strict quality standards worldwide.</string>
    <string name="title_yubi">Be Careful not to Get Your Fingers Caught</string>
    <string name="text_yubi">Fingers are caught in the door, insertion port, etc., causing injury.</string>
    <string name="title_yukijas">Organic JAS Mark</string>
    <string name="text_yukijas">Registration accreditation body inspects that production conforming to the JAS standard of organic foods is being conducted, and as a result, only certified businesses can affix organic JAS marks. Displaying the name of \"organic\", \"organic\" etc, and attaching indication confusing to agricultural products and agricultural processed foods without this \"organic JAS mark\" are prohibited by law.</string>
    <string name="title_zerii">Royal Jelly\'s Fair Mark</string>
    <string name="text_zerii">This mark will be displayed on the product of the member of the \"National Royal Jelly Fair Trade Council\" that is deemed to be displaying properly in accordance with the \"Fair Competition Agreement on Display of Royal Jelly\".</string>

</resources>
