<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MarkTranslater</string>
    <string name="button_translate">Translate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_translate">TranslateActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_select">SelectActivity</string>

    <string name="title_alumi">アルミニウム</string>
    <string name="text_alumi">アルミ缶のリサイクルを進めるために付けられたマークです。回収されたアルミ缶は、アルミ缶やアルミサッシなど再生地金をつくるために利用されています。</string>
    <string name="title_alumi2">アルミニウム</string>
    <string name="text_alumi2">アルミ缶のリサイクルを進めるために付けられたマークです。回収されたアルミ缶は、アルミ缶やアルミサッシなど再生地金をつくるために利用されています。</string>
    <string name="title_alumi3">アルミニウム</string>
    <string name="text_alumi3">アルミ缶のリサイクルを進めるために付けられたマークです。回収されたアルミ缶は、アルミ缶やアルミサッシなど再生地金をつくるために利用されています。</string>
    <string name="title_alumi4">アルミニウム</string>
    <string name="text_alumi4">アルミ缶のリサイクルを進めるために付けられたマークです。回収されたアルミ缶は、アルミ缶やアルミサッシなど再生地金をつくるために利用されています。</string>
    <string name="title_asc">str</string>
    <string name="text_asc">str</string>
    <string name="title_danboru">Cardboard Recycling Mark</string>
    <string name="text_danboru">This mark is the universal recycling symbol. Recycle mark indicates that \"the cardboard can be recycled.\"</string>
    <string name="title_g">G Mark</string>
    <string name="text_g">As an indicator of \"good design\", this mark continues to play its role over more than half a century since its founding.</string>
    <string name="title_ge">str</string>
    <string name="text_ge">str</string>
    <string name="title_jas">Japanese Agricultural Standard Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jas">This mark is given to products that have passed the inspection by the Japanese Agricultural Standards enacted by Minister of Agriculture、Forestry and Fisheries.</string>
    <string name="title_jdma">str</string>
    <string name="text_jdma">str</string>
    <string name="title_jema">str</string>
    <string name="text_jema">str</string>
    <string name="title_jis">Japanese Industrial Standard Mark</string>
    <string name="text_jis">This mark is given to industrial products that have passed the Japanese Industrial Standards.</string>
    <string name="title_kanbatsuzai">Thinnings Mark</string>
    <string name="text_kanbatsuzai">It is the mark that can be displayed on the product using the thinnings.It is the mark to promote the importance of the use of such propulsion and thinnings of thinning and to contribute to the product selection of the consumer.There are two types of use of the thinned wood products and use in public awareness to the use of the mark.It is a system that the National Forestry Cooperative Federation operates to promote the enhancement of forest productivity and conservative culture of the forest resources of Japan.</string>
    <string name="title_mochi">Made in Japan Paddy Rice Glutinous Rice 100% Mark</string>
    <string name="text_mochi">This mark is displayed in the guaranteed products to be packaged rice cake that has been produced only in rice glutinous rice domestically by \"the national rice cake industrial cooperative.\"</string>
    <string name="title_omiyage">str</string>
    <string name="text_omiyage">str</string>
    <string name="title_online">str</string>
    <string name="text_online">str</string>
    <string name="title_pse">PSE Mark</string>
    <string name="text_pse">In consumer products, about products that to be in danger of especially harm to consumers life and body, it can not be sold, if there is no PSC mark indicating that meet the criteria on which the countries of established technology on it.And if dangerous products have been available on the open market that Japan has the right to order the measures of recovery such as in the production business person.These regulations items subject has a the specific products that self-confirmation is required are obliged and a special specific products inspection of further third-party organization in that.</string>
    <string name="title_r">Recycled Paper Use Mark</string>
    <string name="text_r">It is a voluntary mark indicating the ratio of waste paper pulp blending. Recycled paper pulp content ratio 100% recycled paper is used. It is set by the National Congress for Promotion of Waste Reduction (Current 3R Activity Promotion Forum).</string>
    <string name="title_sample">str</string>
    <string name="text_sample">str</string>
    <string name="title_seisanjas">Production Information Released JAS Mark</string>
    <string name="text_seisanjas">This mark is attached to agricultural products on which information such as beef and pork in which information such as feeding and veterinary medicine administration has been published and agricultural chemicals and fertilizers used by producers are publicly disclosed.</string>
    <string name="title_sek">SEK Mark</string>
    <string name="text_sek">This mark is the certification mark of functional processed textile products. Based on ensuring safety, the General Association of Textile Evaluation Technologies Council is certifying while endeavoring to ensure certain performance.</string>
    <string name="title_shitake">str</string>
    <string name="text_shitake">str</string>
    <string name="title_shouene">str</string>
    <string name="text_shouene">str</string>
    <string name="title_shougai">str</string>
    <string name="text_shougai">str</string>
    <string name="title_st">ST Mark</string>
    <string name="text_st">This mark is an abbreviation for Safety toy. It is attached to products that passed ST standard conformity inspection of toy safety standards, mechanical safety, flammability safety, chemical safety. In the event of an accident in the event of an ST marked toy, we have established a compensation mutual aid system.</string>
    <string name="title_tokubetsu">str</string>
    <string name="text_tokubetsu">str</string>
    <string name="title_tokuho">Foods for Specified Health Uses Mark</string>
    <string name="text_tokuho">Foods for specified health uses is a food that can be expected to aim for a particular health, it contains the functional health component (involvement component) that affect such as the body\'s physiological function. </string>
    <string name="title_tokuteijas">Specific JAS Mark</string>
    <string name="text_tokuteijas">This mark is attached to food that meets the JAS standard for foods that meet the JAS standards for special production and manufacturing methods, or that has a feature in quality etc. compared with similar standard products.</string>
</resources>
